<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Vasilis Kontonis</title>
    <link>https://vkonton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Vasilis Kontonis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vkonton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vkonton.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vkonton.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Vasilis Kontonis Hi! I am a PhD student at the Computer Science Department of University of Wisconsin-Madison, where I am very fortunate to be advised by Professor Christos Tzamos. I am particularly interested in algorithms and theoretical machine learning. Currently, I am working on problems related to efficient robust inference in high dimensions.
Before coming to UW-Madison, I studied Electrical and Computer Engineering at the National Technical University of Athens where I was very lucky to be advised by Professor Dimitris Fotakis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://vkonton.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vkonton.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications  Efficient Truncated Statistics with Unknown Truncation.  Vasilis Kontonis, Christos Tzamos, Manolis Zampetakis  FOCS 2019
 Removing Bias in Maching Learning via Truncated Statistics.  Costantinos Daskalakis, Vasilis Kontonis, Christos Tzamos, Manolis Zampetakis  Manuscript.
 Opinion Dynamics with Limited Information.  Fotakis Dimitris, Vardis Kandiros, Vasilis Kontonis, Stratis Skoulakis  WINE 2018
 Learning the Distribution of Edges in Graphs whose vertices may Fail.  Fotakis Dimitris, Vasilis Kontonis, Piotr Krysta, Paul Spirakis  Manuscript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://vkonton.github.io/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vkonton.github.io/service/</guid>
      <description>Service Reviewer: STOC, SODA, WINE, ICML, EC, MFCS, TCS, ALT</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://vkonton.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vkonton.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description> Talks  Efficient Truncated Statistics with Unknown Truncation, FOCS 2019, Video
 Learning PBD Powers, ECCO Research Seminar 2017, University of Liverpool
 Learning Theory Study Group, Corelab NTUA, 2017
 Intoduction, No Free Lunch, Bias-Variance Tradeoff VC-Dimension  Convex Optimization Minicourse, Corelab NTUA, 2017
 Convex Problems, LP QP, SOCP SDP, GW MaxCut Vector Optimization, Duality  Programming with Dependent Types, NTUA, 2015
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>